A Guide to the International Society for Third-Sector Research (ISTR) records FA1838
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Voluntas: International Journal of Voluntary and Nonprofit Organizations, 1990-2021; 6; 8.73 Cubic Feet 23 letter document boxes
  - Editorial Board, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 145)
  - Jeremy Kendall, 1998-2001 (Box 15, Folder 146)
  - Book Review Editor (Elke K. Zuern), 2001 (Box 16, Folder 147)
  - Editor Search, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 148)
  - Plenum Publishing Nonprofit Book Series, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 149)
  - Blackwell Publishers, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 150)
  - Marcel Dekker, Inc., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 151)
  - Walter de Gruyter and Co., 1996 (Box 16, Folder 152)
  - General, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 153)
  - Advertising, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 154)
  - Journal Production Issues, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 155)
  - Plenum/Kluwer Ongoing, 1999-2004 (Box 16, Folder 156)
  - Editor Search, 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 157)
  - Editorial Selection Nomination Letters, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 158)
  - Voluntas Symposium, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 159)
  - Voluntas Symposium - Ten Years After: Civil Society and the Third Sector in Central and Eastern Europe, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 160)
  - Voluntas Symposium - Transnational Third Sector Research, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 161)
  - Voluntas Symposium - Transnational Third Sector Research, Bergen, Norway, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 162)
  - Voluntas Symposium - Transnational Third Sector Research, Bergen, Norway - Pictures, undated (Box 17, Folder 162)
  - Sage Publications, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 163)
  - Subscription Pricing Information, 1993-1996 (Box 17, Folder 164)
  - General Correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box 17, Folder 165-166)
  - Advertisements, 2007-2011 (Box 17, Folder 167)
  - Book Reviews, 2007-2009 (Box 17, Folder 168)
  - General Correspondence, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 169)
  - Publisher's Report, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 170)
  - General, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 171)
  - Editorial Board, 2008-2010 (Box 18, Folder 172)
  - SpringerBriefs Series, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 173)
  - Publisher Request for Proposals, 2010-2011 (Box 18, Folder 174)
  - Publishing Consultant, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 175)
  - New Open Access Journal Proposal, 2015 (Box 18, Folder 176)
  - General, 2015 (Box 18, Folder 177)
  - Bernard Enjolras, 2007-2008 (Box 18, Folder 178)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (ISI) Social Science Index, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 179)
  - Editorial Search, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 180)
  - Voluntas Symposium, Copenhagen, 2014 (Box 18, Folder 181)
  - Book Awards, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 182)
  - Publications Committee, 2011-2013 (Box 18, Folder 183)
  - General, 2012 (Box 18, Folder 184)
  - General, 2011-2012 (Box 18, Folder 185)
  - General, 2013 (Box 18, Folder 186)
  - Springer Publishing, 2015-2017 (Box 18, Folder 187)
  - General, 2015-2017 (Box 19, Folder 188)
  - Chain Bridge Consulting, 2016-2017 (Box 19, Folder 189)
  - Routledge Publishing, 2015-2016 (Box 19, Folder 190)
  - General, 2016-2017 (Box 19, Folder 191)
  - Voluntas Symposium - Foundations: An International Research Symposium, Paris, France, 1993 October 21-23 (Box 19, Folder 192)
  - Voluntas, Volumes 1-32, 1990-2021; 6.1
    Subseries 6.1 contains 2 printed copies of volumes 1-32 of ISTR's Voluntas publication.
    - Voluntas - Volume 1, Numbers 1-2, 1990 May-November (Box 23, Folder 249-250)
    - Voluntas - Volume 2, Numbers 1-2, 1991 May-November (Box 23, Folder 251-252)
    - Voluntas - Volume 3, Numbers 1-3, 1992 May-December (Box 23, Folder 253-255)
    - Voulntas - Volume 4, Numbers 1-4, 1993 April-1994 February (Box 23, Folder 256, Box 24, Folder 257-259)
    - Voluntas - Volume 5, Numbers 1-3, 1994 April-December (Box 24, Folder 260-262)
    - Voluntas - Volume 6, Numbers 1-3, 1995 April-December (Box 24, Folder 263-265)
    - Voluntas - Volume 7, Numbers 1-4, 1996 March-December (Box 25, Folder 266-269)
    - Voluntas - Volume 8, Numbers 1-4, 1997 March-December (Box 25, Folder 270-273)
    - Voluntas - Volume 9, Numbers 1-4, 1998 March-December (Box 25, Folder 274-277)
    - Voluntas - Volume 10, Numbers 1-4, 1999 March-December (Box 26, Folder 278-281)
    - Voluntas - Volume 11, Numbers 1-4, 2000 March-December (Box 26, Folder 282-285)
    - Voluntas - Volume 12, Numbers 1-4, 2001 March-December (Box 26, Folder 286-289)
    - Voluntas - Volume 13, Numbers 1-4, 2002 March-December (Box 27, Folder 290-293)
    - Voluntas - Volume 14, Numbers 1-4, 2003 March-December (Box 27, Folder 294-297)
    - Voluntas - Volume 15, Numbers 1-4, 2004 March-December (Box 27, Folder 298-301)
    - Voluntas - Volume 16, Numbers 1-4, 2005 March-December (Box 28, Folder 302-305)
    - Voluntas - Volume 17, Numbers 1-4, 2006 March-December (Box 28, Folder 306-309)
    - Voluntas - Volume 18, Numbers 1-4, 2007 March-December (Box 28, Folder 310-313)
    - Voluntas - Volume 19, Numbers 1-4, 2008 March-December (Box 28, Folder 314-317)
    - Voluntas - Volume 20, Numbers 1-4, 2009 March-December (Box 29, Folder 318-321)
    - Voluntas - Volume 21, Numbers 1-4, 2010 March-December (Box 29, Folder 322-325)
    - Voluntas - Volume 22, Numbers 1-4, 2011 March-December (Box 29, Folder 326-329)
    - Voluntas - Volume 23, Numbers 1-4, 2012 March-December (Box 30, Folder 330-333)
    - Voluntas - Volume 24, Numbers 1-4, 2013 March-December (Box 30, Folder 334-336, Box 31, Folder 337)
    - Voluntas - Volume 25, Numbers 1-4, 2014 February-August (Box 31, Folder 338-341)
    - Voluntas - Volume 26, Numbers 1-6, 2015 February-December (Box 31, Folder 342-343, Box 32, Folder 344-347)
    - Voluntas - Volume 27, Numbers 1-6, 2016 February-December (Box 33, Folder 348-351, Box 34, Folder 352-353)
    - Voluntas - Volume 28, Numbers 1-6, 2017 February-December (Box 34, Folder 354-355, Box 35, Folder 356-359)
    - Voluntas - Volume 29, Numbers 1-6, 2018 February-December (Box 36, Folder 360-365)
    - Voluntas - Volume 30, Numbers 1-6, 2019 February-December (Box 37, Folder 366-371)
    - Voluntas - Volume 31, Numbers 1-6, 2020 February-December (Box 38, Folder 372-377)
    - Voluntas - Volume 32, Numbers 1-6, 2021 February-December (Box 39, Folder 378-383)
      Closed - Open in 2026
- Printed Material, 1993-2020; 7; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
  - Inside ISTR newsletters (Volumes 1-16), 1993-2008 (Box 1, Folder 1-16)
  - Inside ISTR newsletters (Volumes 17-22), 2009-2014 (Box 2, Folder 17-22)
  - Yearbooks, 2016-2017; 2019 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Celebrating ISTR's Tenth Anniversary: Its Past, Current Progress, and Future Prospects, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Third Sector Research by Rupert Taylor, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 31-32)
  - The Role of Volunteering and the Nonprofit Sector in Building Stronger Communities - Second ISTR Asia and Pacific Regional Conference, by Masayuki Deguchi, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Sociedad Civil Y Desarrollo Local - Andres Solari Vicente, Anabel Cruz Santacroce, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 34)